# STEFAN LICĂ

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Software Engineer specializing in C# and Java backends, with complementary expertise in JavaScript and TypeScript frontend development. I'm also enthusiastic about using Python or Golang and doing more DevOps in future projects and opportunities.

## **SKILLS**

```
Languages: C#, Java, Kotlin, TypeScript, JavaScript, CSS, Python, C++, C
Frameworks: .NET, Android, Android Auto, Angular, React
Development: OOP, Algorithms, Agile, LLMs, Unit Testing, Databases
Infrastructure: Linux, Bash, CI/CD, DevOps, Networking
Languages (again): Fluent English (C2), intermediate German (B1~B2), Romanian
```

### **EXPERIENCE**

Full Stack Software Engineer — IAV GmbH, Berlin, DE NOVEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

- Spearheaded a development project alongside approx. 300 developers for the creation of the new infotainment system of a major automotive brand, leading the creation of multiple key features and maintaining direct communication with clients and adjacent teams to ensure task clarity and alignment.
- Performed refinement of feature and bug tickets and **led discussions with clients and leadership to align development timelines** and balance workload.
- Maintained and enhanced the infotainment systems of several major automotive brands which led to increased code quality and the introduction of new key features to the platforms.
- Led the frontend development of an internal tool integrating LLMs into the software requirements process, meeting tight deadlines and collaborating with cross-functional teams and leadership.
- Independently developed multiple dashboards in 6-8 week cycles using Angular, React, TypeScript and JavaScript and onboarded new developers to transition these into full-scale projects.

Full Stack Software Engineer - Dell Inc., Bucharest, RO DECEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2023

- Led efforts to transition from the previous monolithic architecture of the platform to a microservice based architecture as part of a team made of 11 developers and QA engineers.
- Maintained and enhanced an internal backend middleware platform that facilitated communication between multiple services and sanitises information for further use.
- Demonstrated versatility by adapting to multiple tech stacks such as .NET, C#, SQL, HTML, CSS,
   JavaScript and Salesforce Lightning over the course of 2 projects.
- Oversaw production deployments, carried out code reviews, and resolved any emergent difficulties assuring timely completion of requirements.
- Maintained over 90% code test coverage in the projects through automated and integrated testing. Advocated other developers to ensure their code is thoroughly tested to lessen the workload of the QA team.

### **EDUCATION**

#### MSc in Computer Graphics and Software Engineering

2021 - 2023, NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY POLITEHNICA BUCHAREST

Key Courses: Game Development, VR/AR Development, GPGPU Computing, 3D Modelling

#### BSc in Computer Science and Control Systems

2017 - 2021, NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY POLITEHNICA BUCHAREST

Key Courses: OOP Programming, Parallel/Distributed Systems, Data Structures, Computer Graphics